gratefulgoose.com 2014-06-21

# Privacy Policy | Grateful Goose

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, Potential Investments Ltd is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office under registration number Z2973494. We are committed to protecting your privacy and take every precaution with your personal information, only ever using it in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and Electronic Communications (2000/58/EC).

This document explains how we use your data and should be read alongside our Terms of Service. By using the Service as described in our Terms of Service document you are regarded as having read and agreed to this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy you must cease using this website immediately.

You may be asked to submit some personal data such as name, address, email address or social network login when you register with our Websites, enter a competition, post on a forum, comment on a blog, or subscribe to marketing communications. We may also record which pages of the Website you visit and products and services that interest you. All data we collect will be kept securely in accordance with our internal data policy. Primarily, the reason for collecting this data is to enable us to provide our Service to you, to allow you to create a wish list of online products. We may also use this data to provide you with an efficient service, open and run your account and keep you up to date with our latest developments.

In some instances we may request information about another person, for example the name and email address of a family member to share your list with. Before submitting their personal information it is your responsibility to explain how we are planning on using their data and obtain their consent to this use.

Before purchasing an item from someone’s wish list for a Product or Service with a Third Party you should familiarise yourself with their Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy, as they will be acting as Data Controller of your personal information.

Where permitted by Data Protection and Privacy Laws, we may disclose your personal information. We may do this, for example, if we were required by a Government body, A Court, in connection with legal proceedings or in the connection of the sale of the business or part of the business.

## Marketing Communications

If you register with the website, we may ask you if you would like to receive Marketing Communications to keep you up to date with our service or products we think you may be interested in. If you would like to unsubscribe from marketing communications you can do this using the “unsubscribe link” within the email or alternatively contact us and we will remove you from the database.   

If you are an existing customer we will continue to send marketing communications unless you tell us not to.

## Cookies

We use small text files commonly known as cookies in order to collect information on the performance of our Website. Personal information is not collected; the data simply allow us to monitor how well our Website is working and insights to improve the user experience. Information on cookies can be found here <http://www.aboutcookies.org/>

If you do not want us to use cookies in this way you may disable their use (for more information on how to do this visit [www.dma.org.uk](http://www.dma.org.uk/)) If you do not disable cookies, you are consenting to their use on this Website. Please note if you do disable cookies the performance of the website may be affected and you may not be able to take advantage of the full range of services we offer.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or about the information we hold about you please contact us in the first instance.

You have the right to request a copy of the data we hold about you under the Data Protection Act, please note we reserve the right to charge an administration fee for any request.

These terms constitute the full agreement between you and Potential Investments Ltd, who own and operate gratefulgoose.com and may only be amended in writing. They apply to the exclusion of all other Terms or Conditions of contract proposed.
